BGM
I just ate at Panco Spur for the Legion's project!
Thanks for the food
Eggs, Ippenchan!
I had 760 cups in all, thank you very much for the food. Still one more egg. One egg.
All in all, 760 cups.
Yes. We have had it.
That's amazing, isn't it?
You must have eaten a lot.
I ate a lot.
That's right.
We all made our quota.
We were all aiming for 60 drinks.
That's right.
So we achieved it.
That's right. Everyone exceeded it. That was the goal for now, right?
The thumbnail photo looks very impressive. It makes me want to look at it.
I didn't even ask you to give me a plate of food.
I'm glad you didn't! It's been a long time since we all came to a free event in the first place.
Iwate itself was fun!
It was fun.
It's fun.
How's it going?
Shinju-chan
It was fun.
It was.
And... it was really good.
Oh!
I'm so full.
You're full?
Yeah, I am.
That's good.
And good.
Who's next?
Karen. Next to her is Karen.
Karen? Rine-chan.
What about Sher Beauty? How was it?
I'm full.
You certainly ate the most, didn't you?
I've already had 100.
Well, if you're going to go through all that trouble...
I'm sure you'll do great.
I'm impressed.
You're very athletic, aren't you?
Yeah, I'm sure.
What do you mean?
She's athletic.
She ate a lot of soba noodles.
That's what I'm talking about.
The competition type.
Athletic
So cool!
Yeah, it is.
And?
Tachibana.
Yes, I'm Tachibana.
I've always wanted to try wanko soba,
I was so happy that we all came to eat it this time.
I felt like I was in my youth.
I'm glad.
I would be happy if we could try something like this again.
Thank you for the food.
Hi.
This was the second time for Rune-chan.
The last time we did this, we had 47 cups
but this time she got 78!
She has grown so much!
She has grown!
That's great!
And I'm from Iwate.
The last time I had it...
Let's see...
Ninety.
That's my mom.
Mom.
Mom, that's amazing.
I was 74 or something.I was 74 or something.
This time it was 94.
That's great!
I'm catching up with my mom.
That's for sure.
So
V is great. I caught up with Mom. For sure. So, V!
This project is from you, Mon-chan, isn't it?
That's right.
When I saw that Yate was selected,
Mom saw that Yate was chosen.
She saw it and said, "You should do it.
She said, "You should do it,
I thought that Hina should do it, too,
So I thought, "You should do it. So, you should do it.
Classy.
To the great people of Sendai,
The bigwigs in Sendai?
To the big man at the office,
I told him he should do it,
He said, "Yes, you should.
I said, "Yes, you're right.
He said, "Yes, I agree,
And it came true,
I realized that words are magic.
I'm glad. Thank you for organizing this.
Thank you.
And you, too, Mom.
And Mr. Chino.
I ate 65 bowls.
I've never had so many noodles in my stomach.
You're right, Chino, I'm a rice person.
Next time, I want to have all-you-can-eat barbeque.
That would be nice. And I thought all-you-can-eat or something like that would be nice.
I'm thinking, "I'd love to have all-you-can-eat barbecue.
Yes, you should try it, too.
I think I'm...
I thought I was a sigh of relief. I thought so.
I thought so. You thought so. You thought so.
But with these numbers,
I have proof that I can eat a lot,
I was able to eat a lot of food. I'm happy to have that proof,
I am happy to have that proof.
It's true.
It was delicious. Thank you for the food.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I was aiming for 100 cups, but since this is an off shot, I'll just say that I'm feeling a little better today, and I'm not doing so well.
Yes, the last few days have been strange, but I wanted to do my best, so I did my best, but I had 84 cups...3 cups...2 cups...0 cups...0 cups...0 cups...0 cups...0 cups...0 cups...0 cups...
Zero.
But I think my stomach wasn't strong enough to handle it in the first place.
I'm going to do some stomach training.
Great.
I'd like to do stomach training and try to eat more until I can eat more.
The soba noodles were really good!
The tuna was delicious!
It was so good I hope you'll try it in Iwate and report back to me.
I practiced eating soba last night.
So I was stoic.
That's right.
I'm a gal, so I thought I'd eat at 109 in Shibuya... but maybe I overestimated myself. I hope that many of you will come to visit us from this rocky place.
I hope we can do something like this again, something unique to Tohoku.
I really wanted to go to Shizukuishi in Iwate.
I really wanted to go to Shizukuishi, Iwate.
We have to do a second event.
I know, right?
You know, we always do the Gundan in Miyagi, don't we? We are mainly active in Miyagi.
But since we say we are a Tohoku group, we have to go to all six prefectures.
That's right.
Maybe we should go to Aomori too. I want to go to Aomori, too! And Akita, too. Boo hoo!
Boo-boo!
I'm not a perpetrator of this kind of learning, but every time I go out for a bit, it's nice because it's been a long time since the nine of us have done a project together.
I'd like to do my best at SobaBawa.
I'm not going to say anything if someone I know starts showing it to me.
I can't say anything.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea.
I'm tired and I'm full so I'm going to go home after a good night's sleep
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a good night's sleep.
I'll be icing you! Where! Icing!
That's all I have to say.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.bye-bye
you